wpmayor.com 2019-05-24

# Privacy Policy - WP Mayor

Your privacy is very important to us. At WP Mayor we have a few fundamental principles that we follow:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of our site.

This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information received and collected by WP Mayor and how it is used.

## Website Visitors

Like most website operators, WP Mayor collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. WP Mayor’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how  visitors use the website. From time to time, WP Mayor may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

WP Mayor also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on our blogs. WP Mayor only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that blog commenter IP addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog where the comment was left.

## **Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**

Certain visitors to WP Mayor choose to interact with the website in ways that require WP Mayor to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that WP Mayor gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who comment on our blog to provide a username and email address. Those who wish to receive WP Mayor updates via email, we collect their emails.

In each case, WPMayor collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with the website. WP Mayor does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. Visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

## **Aggregated Statistics**

WP Mayor may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, WP Mayor may monitor the most popular pages on the site or use spam screened by the Akismet service to help identify spam. WP Mayor may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, WP Mayor does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

## **Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information**

WP Mayor discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on WP Mayor’s behalf, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using the WP Mayor website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them.

WP Mayor will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, WP Mayor discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when WP Mayor believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of WP Mayor, third parties or the public at large.

If you are a registered user of the WP Mayor website and have supplied your email address, WP Mayor may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with WP Mayor and our products and services.

If you send us a request (for example via our contact form or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. WP Mayor takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

## **Cookies & Your Personal Data**

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns.

Any personal data provided to or collected by WP Mayor via cookies and other tracking technologies is controlled by RebelCode Ltd, the company behind WP Mayor. WP Mayor uses cookies to help us identify and track visitors, their usage of the WP Mayor website, and their website access preferences.

  * We don’t collect any personal information from you unless you supply it and we need it (for example, signing up to our email newsletter).
  * We won’t share your personal information with anyone else, except when required by some third party services who provide services, such as sending out our email newsletter.
  * We don’t store your personal information on our servers except when necessary for the functioning of the website (for example, the information you enter when leaving a comment).
  * We may share generic aggregated demographic information, not linked to any personal identification information, regarding visitors and users, with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers.

On WP Mayor we use Google Analytics cookies. These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use our website. We use this information to compile reports and to help us improve the website. These cookies collect information in an anonymous form, such as the number of visitors to the website, where visitors have come to the website from and the pages they visited. We do not share personal data with Google.

WP Mayor visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using the WP Mayor website, with the drawback that certain features of the website may not function properly without the aid of cookies. Please check the user guide for your web browser to see how to do this.

## **Business Transfers**

If WP Mayor, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that WP Mayor goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of WP Mayor may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

## **Ads**

Ads appearing on WP Mayor may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by WP Mayor and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

## Privacy Policy Acceptance

By using this website, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. Although most changes are likely to be minor, WP Mayor may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in WP Mayor’s sole discretion. WP Mayor encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us by email at info@wpmayor.com.
